https://www.amateurcool.com/static/privacy

AMATEUR SOCIAL NET
Categories:
AmateurAnalArabAsianAssBBWBDSMBig DickBig TitsBlowjobCreampieCuckoldCumshotDpEbonyEmoFacialsFemdomFetishFistingFlexibleFootGangbangGayGirlfriendsGranniesGroupHairyHandjobsHardcoreInterracialLatinasLesbiansLingerieMasturbateMatureMilfMuffdivingOrgyOutdoorPartyPeeingPovPregnantPublicRedheadRimmingShavedShemaleSmall TitsSquirtingStrippingSwingersTeenThreesomeToysUniformVoyeurWebcamsWives
Home |
Videos |
Photos |
Amateur Nude Social Network
Categories
Newest Porn |
Most Popular |
Top Rated
AmateurCool - Privacy policy
AmateurCool.com respects your privacy and we stand by the national privacy rules. Personal information is collected only as much as it is technically necessary. In no case will these data be sold or given to others. The following terms of contract give you an overview of how we intend to protect your privacy and which kind of data is collected for which purposes.
Data collection on this web page
AmateurCool.com automatically collects and saves information from your browser in our server log files. These include:
-Browser type and version
-Used operating system
-Referrer URL (last visited website)
-IP address / host name of your computer
-Time of access
There is no merging of this data with other data sources, collected data is also deleted after a statistical analysis.
Cookies
Our web page uses cookies in several places. With the help of these cookies our web page should become more user-friendly, more effective and more secure. For example we use cookies to store your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include the ability to login to a personal account to save videos, leave comments and utilize other advanced features. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer by your browser. Cookies cannot do any harm to your computer and cannot contain viruses or malware.
Google Analytics
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ('Google'). Google Analytics uses 'cookies', which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information on behalf of the operator of this website for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing them other services relating to website activity and internet usage. The IP-address, that your Browser conveys within the scope of Google Analytics, will not be associated with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. You can also opt-out from being tracked by Google Analytics with effect for the future by downloading and installing Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Addon for your current web browser: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en.
Advertising networks
Third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.AmateurCool.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. AmateurCool has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. AmateurCool's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.
Right of disclosure
You have the right to be informed any time about the data saved concerning your person, its origin and receiver as well as the purpose of saving. Disclosure is given by AmateurCool.com.
Further information
Your trust in us is important to us. That is why we want to inform you about the usage of personal data. If you have questions that could not be answered in this privacy policy declaration or if you want further information, just contact AmateurCool.
Cool Free Sites
persiankitty
homemadevideos
swapsmutporn
libraryofthumbs
indienudes
amateursgonewild
ilovemovies
